SANTIAGO BERNAL URIBE

Graduated from the University of Central as Electronic Engineer. During my personal training and experience within the companies worked, I managed to incorporate knowledge in telecommunications, bioengineering, nanotechnology, automation and control, among others; with the ability to solve complex problems by applying principles of electronic engineering, science and mathematics, and generating innovative technological solutions with socio-environmental responsibility, which meet needs.

sberna lu@ucen tral.ed u.co





Bogotá D.C., Colomb



i

www.li nkedin .com/ in/ santia gobern



WORK EXPERIENCE

Jr Analyst
UBITS LEARNING
SOLUTIONS

03/28/2022 - 09/20/2022 Bogotá D.C., Colombia null

Collection Advisor C.A.C ABOGADOS

08/07/2018 - 12/18/2018 Bogotá D.C., Colombia null

Cash Assistant
PERMODA LTDA

11/26/2019 - 12/31/2019 Bogotá D.C., Colombia null

teller

Davivienda

05/02/2017 - 05/08/2018 Bogotá D.C., Colombia

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

Técnico en Asesoría comercial y operaciones en entidades financieras

2017

SENA

Técnico en Asistencia Administrativa

2016

SENA

WORK EXPERIENCE

null

EDUCATION

INGENIERÍA ELECTRÓNICA UNIVERSIDAD CENTRAL COLOMBIA 08/2022

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS